UNITE President's Office Files 6000/010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Pension Funds, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Philadelphia Workers Education Center, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Prescription Drugs (Alliance for Retired Americans), 2001 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Reich, Robert, Former Secretary of Labor, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Schrader, Abe, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Shanker, Albert, Memorial Service, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Smithsonian Labor Exhibit, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Springer - Kemp, Maida, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Steelworkers Support Rally, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Sweatshops - Anti-sweatshop Rally, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Sweatshops - Anti-sweatshop Committee, 1999-2001 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Sweatshops - NYC Procurement Press Conference, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Sweatshops - New Jersey, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Sweatshops - Nike, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Sweatshops - United Students Against Sweatshops, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Sweatshops, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Sweatshops, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Sweatshops - American Federation of Teachers, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Sweatshops - Day of Conscience, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Sweatshops - Independent Monitoring Conference, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Sweatshops - NYS - Spano Hearing, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Sweatshops - Pataki Proposal, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Sweatshops - Stop Sweatshops Act - Press Conference, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Sweatshops - IUD Conference, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Sweatshops - National Consumers League (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Sweeney, John, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- Trade Legislation - HR 2149, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- Union Health Center, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Union Health Center, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- United Federation of Teachers (UFT), 2001 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- United Nations, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Village Independent Democrats, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Vote, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Wagner Archives Speech, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- White House Apparel Industry Partnership, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Work in America Institute, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Workers Defense League, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Workman's Circle, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- World Economic Forum, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- ILGWU/UNITE - General Executive Brand, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- ILGWU/UNITE - General Executive Board (GEB), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council - Corporate Transactions Presentation (Mazur), 1997 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council Meeting, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council and General Board Special Meeting, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Issues for Sohn Sweeney Meeting, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Trade Subcommittee Meeting, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- AFL-CIO Senior Action Committee, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council Committee, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- AFL-CIO Executive Meeting, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  Feb. 19-22
- AFL-CIO, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Special Procedures for Article XX, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Minutes of Executive Council Meeting, Statements adopted by the Executive Council, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- AFL-CIO Program Summary & Budget Proposal, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Parmalat/Farmland Article XXI, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- AFL-CIO Article XX and XXI Review (Box 13, Folder 33)
- UNITE/XXI of the AFL-CIO Constitution (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Burma, AFL-CIO (Box 13, Folder 35)
- AFL-CIO Travel Policy (Box 13, Folder 36)
- AFL-CIO Committee, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Committee Infrastructure, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- AFL-CIO Tax Cuts v. Medicare Other Congressional Issues, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- File Cuba AFL-CIO (Box 13, Folder 40)
- John Sweeney, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- East Natural Food Market (Box 14, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council Meeting, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council Committee Names Addresses, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council Meeting, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Memo, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Memo, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Executive Council AFL-CIO, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Mazur Statements, Memos, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Greater Blouse (Box 14, Folder 8)
- NAFTA AFL-CIO Briefing Packet (Box 14, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council Committee, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO Membership Report, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- John Sweeney's Remarks (Box 14, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- John Sweeney White House, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- John Sweeney White House, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- John Sweeney, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- John Sweeney / Andrew Young, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Manufacturing Matters Impact/Productivity Growth, Wages & Income Dist., 1999 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Policy Statements - AFL-CIO XX (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Politics (Box 14, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO Organizing Meeting Plan, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- AFL-CIO Organizing, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Jay Mazur UNITE AFL-CIO Pension Fund Trustees Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  September 19, 1997
- Political & Organizing Program, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Trumka Committee on Labor and the Environment, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Retired Workers Organizing, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- AFL-CIO David Smith, Director Public Policy, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Strategic Organizing Campaign (Box 14, Folder 27)
- AFL-CIO Strategic Approaches Committee Mission Statement, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Students Against Sweatshops, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- AFL-CIO Trade Partnership Act, Title II, U.S. Caribbean of theTrade and Development Act, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Richard Trumka, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Union Labor Life Insurance Company (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Jay Mazur, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Jay Mazur, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Jay Mazur, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  March-August
- Jay Mazur, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  October/November
- See Jay Mazur (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Jay Mazur, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  May 19
- Jay Mazur, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  May/June
- Jay Mazur, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  February
- Jay Mazur, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- C.J. April-June, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- See Jay, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- ACTPN, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Work for America Institute Conference May 13-16, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- GEB Commission of Long Term Contracts, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Carhatt, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- New Alliance, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- SEIU Requests, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- CUNY Commission, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- GEB UNITE Board Meeting, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- New Trade Strategy (Susan Cowell)(GEB UNITE), 1992 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- UNITE Executive Session Convention June, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- GEB Meeting, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  February 10
- GEB Meeting, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  June
- GEB Meeting, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  October
- GEB Minutes and Attachments, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  May
- GEB Meeting, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  June 18-21
- GEB Minutes and Attachments, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Meeting, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- GEB September, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- GEB Meeting, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  October 31
- GEB Meeting, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- GEB Meeting, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  December 18
- GEB Meeting, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  December 11
- GEB Minutes, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  June 30
- GEB Executive Committee, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  July 12
- GEB, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  December
- GEB, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- GEB - Mazur Farewell Address, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- GEB Mazur Farewell Address, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- John McFadden III Appeal, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- UNITE British Columbia Jt. Council Resolution (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Local 1948-3 Appeal and Resolutions (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Local 155 Re-affiliation Resolutions, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Executive Committee, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  January 20
- GEB Topics, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Executive Committee Meeting, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  March 7
- GEB Meeting, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Commission (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Executive Council Minutes, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Recent Press Comments on Fast Track, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  November
- Thompson Committee Depositions and Interviews, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  August 11
- AFL-CIO Financial Statements, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Trade Committee AFL-CIO (Box 15, Folder 42)
- International Organizing, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 43)
- John Sweeney Post Election Poll of Union Members - More Election Updates, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 44)
- AFL-CIO Boskin Commission Report, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Fast Tract Legislation, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  September 18
- AFL-CIO February - March, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- News Articles AFL-CIO, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Report of the Trade Subcommittee (Box 16, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Election AFL-CIO, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO Older and Retired Workers, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Social Security Advisory Council - Release, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO Council Meeting - Chicago, IL, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  August 5-6
- ILO Home Work Convention (John Sweeney) (Box 16, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO Organizing Solidarity, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- AFL-CIO Economic Education, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- AFL-CIO Election Results Political Department, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Memos and Agenda, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Fran Reiter Meeting (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Reiter Task Force, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Long Term, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- GEB Files for Jay, 1995-1999 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Jay Mazur and Carl Proper Memos (Box 16, Folder 21)
- WTI Meeting Agenda and Reports, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Jay Mazur, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  July
- Letter to Mazur from Manhattan Pres., 1997 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  March
- Jay Mazur - GIDC Fundraising, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Report on CUNY Ban Association of NYC, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- UNITE Memos - Invoice for [TC] and CAF Fund (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Memos, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Memos - Howard Daniels, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Jay Mazur / Citizens Union, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Jay Mazur / Citizens Union, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Apparel Industry Partnership Anti-sweatshop Campaign (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Master Agreements, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- End Master Agreements, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Klein Hilfiger Sale, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- GIDC Budget, Apparel Industry News, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  February - March
- Office Memos, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Randy Levine Communications, 1997-1999 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Correspondence with Giuliani Administration Meetings (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Correspondence with AFL-CIO and WTI, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 40)
- Inter-Office Correspondence with Carl Proper, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 41)